# Function to read the name
def read_name():
""" ... """
Function to read the user name.
Returns:
str: The user name.
name = input("Enter your name: ")
return name
# Function to read the address
def read_address():
""" ... """
Function to read the user's address.
Returns:
str: The user's address.
address = input("Enter your address: ")
return address
# Function to read the phone
def read_phone():
""" ... """
Function to read the user's phone number.
Returns:
str: The user's phone number.
telephone = input("Enter your phone: ")
return telephone
# Main function to read the name, address, telephone and print on the screen.
name = read_name()
address = read_address()
telephone = read_phone()
# Print user data
print(f"Name: ")
print(f"Address: ")
print(f"Telephone: ")
if __name__ == "__main__":
main()